[
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- At a 2019 Kennedy Center Honors event the then Secretary of State Mike Pompeo was called out by this 70's era soft-rock singer and honoree for being an enabler to President Trump.",
        "correct": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerA": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerB": "Debbie Boone",
        "answerC": "Joan Biaz",
        "answerD": "Olivia Newton- John"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2001 this norteño band from San José, California sang \"Let me remind the gringo, that I didn't cross the border, the border crossed me.\"",
        "correct": "Los Tigres del Norte",
        "answerA": "Los Tigres del Norte",
        "answerB": "Los Tucanes de Tijuana",
        "answerC": "Intocable",
        "answerD": "Vicente \"Chente\" Fernández "
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1985 what British weekly music magazine voted the landmark political album \"What's Going On\" by Marvin Gaye the best album of all time? ",
        "correct": "NME",
        "answerA": "NME",
        "answerB": "The Globe",
        "answerC": "Melody Maker",
        "answerD": "Melody Maker"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who is considered the first author of the 1901 civil rights anthem \"We Shall Overcome\"? ",
        "correct": "Claude McKay",
        "answerA": "Claude McKay",
        "answerB": "Charles Tindley",
        "answerC": "Countee Cullen",
        "answerD": "James Weldon Johnson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk punk artist, and champion of feminist causes, began her music career by starting her own record label- Righteous Babe Records. Who is the Artist?",
        "correct": "Ani DiFranco",
        "answerA": "Ani DiFranco",
        "answerB": "Lucinda Williams",
        "answerC": "Tori Amos",
        "answerD": "Laura Jane Grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the Temptations song about the sad state of the world \"Ball of Confusion\" come out?",
        "correct": "1970",
        "answerA": "1970",
        "answerB": "1943",
        "answerC": "1990",
        "answerD": "1964"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The synth- rock band Depeche Mode released this atheist friendly hit in 1984 that mocked \"God's sick sense of humor.\" ",
        "correct": "\"Blasphemous Rumors\"",
        "answerA": "\"Blasphemous Rumors\"",
        "answerB": "\"Master and Servant\"",
        "answerC": "\"Flies on the Windscreen\"",
        "answerD": "\"Personal Jesus\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1986 album Lives in the Balance, a record full of songs critical of U.S. imperialism and militarism, is perhaps the most political album by this U.S. rock musician and singer.",
        "correct": "Jackson Brown",
        "answerA": "Jackson Brown",
        "answerB": "James Taylor",
        "answerC": "Don Henley",
        "answerD": "Tom Petty"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This female R&B artist from Texas was arrested in 2010, and charged with disorderly conduct for appearing nude in Dealey Plaza in Dallas for a video shoot.",
        "correct": "Erykah Badu",
        "answerA": "Erykah Badu",
        "answerB": "Jill Scott",
        "answerC": "Mary J Blige",
        "answerD": "Lauryn Hill"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This artist recorded the song \"Freedom is Free\" in 2017 to counter the notion that war and death are necessary costs for freedom. ",
        "correct": "Chicano Batman",
        "answerA": "Chicano Batman",
        "answerB": "Ozomatli",
        "answerC": "Bardo Martinez",
        "answerD": "Styx"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Nina Hagen's 1983 hit \"99 Red Balloons\" was about what? ",
        "correct": "Cold war paranoia",
        "answerA": "Cold war paranoia",
        "answerB": "Fascist paranoia",
        "answerC": "White supremacist paranoia",
        "answerD": "War on terror paranoia"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- How did the radical, folk musician Phil Ochs die?",
        "correct": "Suicide",
        "answerA": "Suicide",
        "answerB": "Murder",
        "answerC": "AIDS",
        "answerD": "Cancer"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The country singer Tim McGraw described himself as what type of Democrat in 2008?",
        "correct": "Blue Dog",
        "answerA": "Blue Dog",
        "answerB": "Southern",
        "answerC": "Conservative",
        "answerD": "Progressive"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Donna Summer and  Barbara Streisand teamed up to record this women's rights song in 1979.",
        "correct": "\"No More Tears (Enough is Enough)\"",
        "answerA": "\"No More Tears (Enough is Enough)\"",
        "answerB": "\"(I'm a) Stand Up Women\"",
        "answerC": "\"I Am a Women\"",
        "answerD": "\"I Will Survive LA\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk rock duo performed a concert in the spring in 2016 to protest the United Methodist Church's ban on  permitting same-sex couples to marry.",
        "correct": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerA": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerB": "Ann and Nancy Wilson",
        "answerC": "Shakespeare's Sister",
        "answerD": "Ann and Nancy Wilson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This famous 1970's pop and blues singer said in 2018;  \"There's climate in the Republican Party of complicity with the leader of the country, who is inspiring people to violence.\"",
        "correct": "Carol King",
        "answerA": "Carol King",
        "answerB": "Debbie Boone",
        "answerC": "Anne Murray",
        "answerD": "Carly Simon"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This best selling singer, popular in the 1970's and early 80's, was a big supporter of Bill Clinton in his 1992 bid for the White House and became a close family friend.",
        "correct": "Barbara Streisand",
        "answerA": "Barbara Streisand",
        "answerB": "Bette Midler",
        "answerC": "Cher",
        "answerD": "Liza Minelli"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Avant Grade singer Diamanda Galás was a member of what direct action organization in the 1980's?",
        "correct": "ACT UP",
        "answerA": "ACT UP",
        "answerB": "The National Organization of Women",
        "answerC": "Queer Nation",
        "answerD": "Human Rights Campaign"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who started Band Aid?",
        "correct": "Bob Geldof and Midge Ure",
        "answerA": "Bob Geldof and Midge Ure",
        "answerB": "Boy George and Midge Ure",
        "answerC": "Bono and Jim Kerr",
        "answerD": "Bob Geldof and Bono"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which black female singing group recorded the song \"Independent Women (Part 1)\"? ",
        "correct": "Destiny's Child",
        "answerA": "Destiny's Child",
        "answerB": "TLC",
        "answerC": "Salt -n- Pepa",
        "answerD": "En Vouge"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What's the name of radical folk singer Billy Bragg's first album?",
        "correct": "Life's Riot With Spy vs Spy",
        "answerA": "Life's Riot With Spy vs Spy",
        "answerB": "Don't Try This at Home",
        "answerC": "England, Half English",
        "answerD": "Worker's Playtime"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This androgynous hip-hop, and psychedelic soul artist has been considered a lead innovator in the afro-futurist movement.",
        "correct": "Janelle Monae",
        "answerA": "Janelle Monae",
        "answerB": "Grace Jones",
        "answerC": "Cynthia Erivo",
        "answerD": "Tessa Thompson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The folk trio Peter, Paul and Mary recorded the top ten hit \"If I Had a Hammer\" in 1962. Who originally wrote the song?",
        "correct": "Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes",
        "answerA": "Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes",
        "answerB": "Woody Guthrie",
        "answerC": "Phil Ochs",
        "answerD": "Millard Lampell and Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the all gay, synth trio Bronski Beat form in England?",
        "correct": "1983",
        "answerA": "1983",
        "answerB": "1990",
        "answerC": "1967",
        "answerD": "2010"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1939 the organization Daughters of the American Revolution refused to let this black opera singer perform at their concert venue, Constitution Hall, because she was black.",
        "correct": "Marian Anderson",
        "answerA": "Marian Anderson",
        "answerB": "Sarah Vaughan",
        "answerC": "Lena Horne",
        "answerD": "Ella Fitzgerald"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- America singer Lena Horne, worked with this first lady in the 1940's around anti-lynching legislation.",
        "correct": "Elenore Roosevelt",
        "answerA": "Elenore Roosevelt",
        "answerB": "Lou Henry Hoover",
        "answerC": "Mamie Eisenhower",
        "answerD": "Bess Truman"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In Madonna's 1989 video like \"Like a Prayer\" a black man is falsely arrested for what? ",
        "correct": "Killing a white girl",
        "answerA": "Killing a white girl",
        "answerB": "Marrying a white girl in the 1920's",
        "answerC": "Raping a white girl",
        "answerD": "Staring at a white girl"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The song \"Why?\", a 1984 hit song by the group Bronski Beat about anti-gay prejudice and hate appeared on what important album?",
        "correct": "Age of Consent",
        "answerA": "Age of Consent",
        "answerB": "Truthdare Doubledare",
        "answerC": "Rainbow Nation",
        "answerD": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the music effort \"Band Aid\" begin? ",
        "correct": "1984",
        "answerA": "1984",
        "answerB": "1999",
        "answerC": "1971",
        "answerD": "2013"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The jazz oratorio piece \"Blood on the Fields\" about black chattel slavery in the U.S. was written by which jazz traditionalist popular in the early 1980's? ",
        "correct": "Wynton Marsalis",
        "answerA": "Wynton Marsalis",
        "answerB": "Herbie Hancock",
        "answerC": "Miles Davis",
        "answerD": "Wayne Shorter"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Dr. Bernice Johnson Reagon founded this  all-female, African-American cappella ensemble.",
        "correct": "Sweet Honey in the Rock",
        "answerA": "Sweet Honey in the Rock",
        "answerB": "The Shirelles",
        "answerC": "The Supremes",
        "answerD": "The Chiffons"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What train did the British singer and song writer Cat Stevens want people to get on in 1971?",
        "correct": "The peace train",
        "answerA": "The peace train",
        "answerB": "The party train",
        "answerC": "The last train",
        "answerD": "The A train"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1986 Nina Hagen teamed up with this new wave artist to record the song \"Don't Kill the Animals.\" Who was the other musician?",
        "correct": "Lene Lovich",
        "answerA": "Lene Lovich",
        "answerB": "Laurie Anderson",
        "answerC": "Joan Jett",
        "answerD": "Debbie Harry"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- New York singer Diamanda Galás's Masque of the Red Death, released in 1989 was about what subject?",
        "correct": "The AIDS crisis",
        "answerA": "The AIDS crisis",
        "answerB": "The West Nile Virus",
        "answerC": "The COVID 19 Virus",
        "answerD": "The Ebola Virus"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What was the name of country singer/ songwriter Steve Earle's 2004 song about revolution?",
        "correct": "\"The Revolution Starts Now\"",
        "answerA": "\"The Revolution Starts Now\"",
        "answerB": "\"I Am the Revolution\"",
        "answerC": "\"I'm Waiting For the Revolution\"",
        "answerD": "\"We are the Revolution\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Salman Ramadan Abedi killed 23 people and wounded over 139 at a May 22, 2017 pop concert in a bombing attack in Manchester, England. Who was the performer?",
        "correct": "Ariana Grande",
        "answerA": "Ariana Grande",
        "answerB": "Lady Gaga",
        "answerC": "J- Lo",
        "answerD": "Selena Gomez"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The title of the Michael Eric Dyson book \"Make Me Wanna Holla\" was taken from what artist's 1971 song? ",
        "correct": "Marvin Gaye/ Inner City Blues",
        "answerA": "Marvin Gaye/ Inner City Blues",
        "answerB": "Smokey Robinson/ Holla",
        "answerC": "Stevie Wonder/ Livin' for the City",
        "answerD": "Jackie Wilson/ Throw up My Hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What label did the funk, rock, and R&B musician Me'Shell NdegeOcello sign with in the early 1990's?",
        "correct": "Maverick Records",
        "answerA": "Maverick Records",
        "answerB": "Sony Records",
        "answerC": "2- Tone Records",
        "answerD": "Arista Records"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Swing Low, Sweet Cadillac, a 1967 live recording from American jazz trumpeter Dizzy Gillespie was about what?",
        "correct": "The cultural journey of black slaves in the U.S. from an African identity to an American one.",
        "answerA": "The cultural journey of black slaves in the U.S. from an African identity to an American one.",
        "answerB": "The end of African American slavery in the United States in 1965 and its aftermath",
        "answerC": "The music revolution that started in Motown Detriot- the manufacturing center of Cadillac",
        "answerD": "The horrors of the Middle Passage for African slaves in their transport to the U.S."
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This 2017 album by Hurry for the Riff Raff contained the alternative hit \"Palante\", about the struggles of everyday peoples in the face of colonialism from a Puerto Rican perspective.",
        "correct": "The Navigator",
        "answerA": "The Navigator",
        "answerB": "Look Out Mama",
        "answerC": "My Dearest Darkest",
        "answerD": "Small Town Heroes"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which country singer said in 2015 \"I'm a great Bernie and Hillary fan, you know?\"",
        "correct": "Willie Nelson",
        "answerA": "Willie Nelson",
        "answerB": "Tim McGraw",
        "answerC": "Toby Keith",
        "answerD": "Keith Urban"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1970 song \"Big Yellow Taxi\" by folk singer-songwriter Joni Mitchell was about what?",
        "correct": "Environmental  Degradation",
        "answerA": "Environmental  Degradation",
        "answerB": "Car Pollution",
        "answerC": "Racism in Canada",
        "answerD": "The Evils of War"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- \"Strange Fruit\", a song about Black lynching's in the U.S., was recorded by this female jazz singer in 1939.",
        "correct": "Billy Holiday",
        "answerA": "Billy Holiday",
        "answerB": "Ella Fitzgerald",
        "answerC": "Sarah Vaughan",
        "answerD": "Etta James"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- During a 1977 episode of Sesame Street, who participated in the first representation of breastfeeding ever aired on television?",
        "correct": "Buffy Sainte- Marie",
        "answerA": "Buffy Sainte- Marie",
        "answerB": "Loretta Lynn",
        "answerC": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerD": "Olivia Newton-John"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2019 the record Omoiyari, a concept album about the internment of Japanese Americans during World War II, was released by which Seattle based violinist?",
        "correct": "Kishi Bashi",
        "answerA": "Kishi Bashi",
        "answerB": "Haruomi Hosono",
        "answerC": "Keiji Haino",
        "answerD": "Ami Nakashima"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Annie Lennox, of the synth- pop duo the Eurythmics, partnered with this soul music legend to record the feminist song \"Sisters Are Doing it For Themselves.\"",
        "correct": "Aretha Franklin",
        "answerA": "Aretha Franklin",
        "answerB": "Diana Ross",
        "answerC": "Celine Dion",
        "answerD": "Mariah Carey"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This U.S. composer and innovator in experimental music declared in an 1985 interview that he was an anarchist stating \"I don't like government! And I don't like institutions!\"",
        "correct": "John Cage",
        "answerA": "John Cage",
        "answerB": "Phillip Glass",
        "answerC": "Bryan Ferry",
        "answerD": "Brian Eno"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This influential, Black blues singer and guitarist from Birmingham, Alabama sang \"O'freedom\" at the historic March on Washington for civil rights and jobs.",
        "correct": "Odetta",
        "answerA": "Odetta",
        "answerB": "Lena Horne",
        "answerC": "Eartha Kitt",
        "answerD": "Etta James"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This singer/songwriter released the women's liberation anthem \"I am Women\" in 1971. What's her name?",
        "correct": "Hellen Reddy",
        "answerA": "Hellen Reddy",
        "answerB": "Olivia Newton- John",
        "answerC": "Anne Murray",
        "answerD": "Leslie Gore"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The U.S. based, 1970's funk band Roy C. Hammond and the Honey Drippers released the song \"Impeach the President.\" What president did they want impeached?",
        "correct": "Richard Nixon",
        "answerA": "Richard Nixon",
        "answerB": "George W Bush",
        "answerC": "Bill Clinton",
        "answerD": "Gerald Ford"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk and blues singer who wrote songs about prison, slavery and being poor and black in the south, was convicted of murder and attempted murder in the early 1900's.",
        "correct": "Lead Belly",
        "answerA": "Lead Belly",
        "answerB": "Howling Wolf",
        "answerC": "Muddy Waters",
        "answerD": "Willie Dixon"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Dionne Warwick recorded this song in 1962 expressing frustration at men in the music industry trying to mold her into something she wasn't. What was the song?",
        "correct": "\"Don't Make Me Over\"",
        "answerA": "\"Don't Make Me Over\"",
        "answerB": "\"You Don't Know Me\"",
        "answerC": "\"I am Me\"",
        "answerD": "\"I Am Who I Am\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Female R&B artist Erykah Badu is a member of what socio-spiritual movement?",
        "correct": "The Five Percent Nation",
        "answerA": "The Five Percent Nation",
        "answerB": "The Santeria Religion",
        "answerC": "The Fruit of Islam",
        "answerD": "The Pentecostals"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The Stevie Wonder song \"Livin' for the City\", a song about the struggles of poor, black inner city youth and the racist system of mass incarceration, first appeared on what 1973 album?",
        "correct": "Innervisions",
        "answerA": "Innervisions",
        "answerB": "Songs in the Key of Life",
        "answerC": "My Cherie Amour",
        "answerD": "Talking Book"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1968 the \"Godfather of Soul\" James Brown released an anthem of the Black Power movement. What song was it? ",
        "correct": "\"Say it Loud I'm Black and I'm Proud\"",
        "answerA": "\"Say it Loud I'm Black and I'm Proud\"",
        "answerB": "\"I've Got You (I Feel Good)\"",
        "answerC": "\"Papa's Got a Brand New Bag\"",
        "answerD": "\"Get Up Offa That Thing\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What two groups named their records \"Steal This Album\" after the 1960's YIPPIE Abbie Hoffman's \"Steal this Book.\" ",
        "correct": "The political hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down",
        "answerA": "The political hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down",
        "answerB": "The political hip- hop group Dead  Prez and the alternative metal band Rage Against the Machine",
        "answerC": "The hip-hop group The Roots and the alternative metal band Faith No More",
        "answerD": "The hip-hop group Gang Star and the alternative metal band Insane Clown Posse"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who wrote and sang \"People Get Ready\", a warm and soulful song released in 1965, inspired by the US  civil rights movement?",
        "correct": "Curtis Mayfield",
        "answerA": "Curtis Mayfield",
        "answerB": "Marvin Gaye",
        "answerC": "Al Green",
        "answerD": "Isaac Hayes"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who sang these lyrics in the 1971 song \"Man in Black\"? \"I wear the black for the poor and beaten down/living in the hopeless, hungry side of town/I wear it for the prisoner who has long paid for his crime/but is there because he's a victim of the time.\"",
        "correct": "Johnny Cash",
        "answerA": "Johnny Cash",
        "answerB": "Waylon Jennings",
        "answerC": "Merle Haggard",
        "answerD": "Kris Kristofferson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The androgynous new wave and soul artist Grace Jones was born in what country?",
        "correct": "Jamaica",
        "answerA": "Jamaica",
        "answerB": "Trinidad and Tobago",
        "answerC": "Dominican Republic",
        "answerD": "Haiti"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Former four term governor of California, Jerry Brown, dated this U.S. based soft-rock singer popular in the 1970's.",
        "correct": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerA": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerB": "Bette Midler",
        "answerC": "Chaka Kahn",
        "answerD": "Patti LaBelle"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The song \"Hello Birmingham\" by radical punk folk artist Ani DiFranco is about what?",
        "correct": "The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama",
        "answerA": "The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama",
        "answerB": "The racist bombing of a Black Church in Birmingham, Alabama",
        "answerC": "The murder of Kansas abortion provider George Tiller in 2009",
        "answerD": "The murder of Florida abortion provider Dr. David Gunn in 1993"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who recorded the 1960 American jazz album \"We Insist! Freedom Now\" ",
        "correct": "Max Roach",
        "answerA": "Max Roach",
        "answerB": "Buddy Rich",
        "answerC": "Neil Peart",
        "answerD": "Art Blakey"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Aretha Franklin released the feminist anthem \"Respect\" in what year?",
        "correct": "1967",
        "answerA": "1967",
        "answerB": "1950",
        "answerC": "1995",
        "answerD": "2003"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1931 organized labor staple \"I Am a Union Women\" was written and sang by who?",
        "correct": "Aunt Molly Jackson",
        "answerA": "Aunt Molly Jackson",
        "answerB": "Bessie Smith",
        "answerC": "Sara Carter",
        "answerD": "Marion Harris"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Donna Summer sang this controversial song in 1978 about sex workers in LA. What was the name of the song?",
        "correct": "\"Bad Girls\"",
        "answerA": "\"Bad Girls\"",
        "answerB": "\"Dim all the Lights\"",
        "answerC": "\"MacArthur Park\"",
        "answerD": "\"Hot Stuff\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In October 2018 this pop artist is generally credited with registering over 166,000 voters across the US with one Instagram message in the run up to election day.",
        "correct": "Taylor Swift",
        "answerA": "Taylor Swift",
        "answerB": "Selena Gomez",
        "answerC": "Beyonce",
        "answerD": "Lady Gaga"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- According to Leonard Cohen in this 1992 song off his album The Future what is coming to USA?",
        "correct": "Democracy",
        "answerA": "Democracy",
        "answerB": "Fascism",
        "answerC": "Socialism",
        "answerD": "A Race War"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In what year did Sweet Honey in the Rock perform at the Obama White House?",
        "correct": "2008",
        "answerA": "2008",
        "answerB": "1999",
        "answerC": "2017",
        "answerD": "2005"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2018 pop singer John Legend came out in support of what Florida state ballot measure?",
        "correct": "Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prison",
        "answerA": "Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prison",
        "answerB": "ACT 12 to reinstate affirmative action in",
        "answerC": "Initiative 204 to ban discrimination against LGBTQ in employment",
        "answerD": "Measure 13 to ban undocumented immigrants from voting"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which famous, Canadian born, folk and jazz singer-songwriter wrote the 1970 song \"Woodstock\"?",
        "correct": "Joni Mitchell",
        "answerA": "Joni Mitchell",
        "answerB": "Janis Joplin",
        "answerC": "Mama Cass",
        "answerD": "Carol Carpenter"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- The pop star Lady Gaga won the MTV Video Music Award for Best Female Video in 2011 for this pro LGBTQI song.",
        "correct": "\"Born This Way\"",
        "answerA": "\"Born This Way\"",
        "answerB": "\"I'm Coming Out\"",
        "answerC": "\"Hair\"",
        "answerD": "\"Kiss Me I'm Queer\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- This former boy band superstar was arrested on stage in Georgia for simulating sex on a bed with audience members.",
        "correct": "Bobby Brown",
        "answerA": "Bobby Brown",
        "answerB": "Donnie Wahlberg",
        "answerC": "Joe Jonas",
        "answerD": "Chris Sellers"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUISC MIX- In 1996, she started a philanthropic non-profit fund Nihewan Foundation for American Indian Education devoted to improving Native American students participation in learning.",
        "correct": "Buffy Sainte-Marie",
        "answerA": "Buffy Sainte-Marie",
        "answerB": "Joni Michell",
        "answerC": "Tanya Tagaq",
        "answerD": "Joan Baez"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What's the name of the Mitt Romney dog that the new wave band Devo sang about wanting to save from the roof of his car on family outings during the 2012 presidential race?",
        "correct": "Seamus",
        "answerA": "Seamus",
        "answerB": "Mutt",
        "answerC": "Goldwater",
        "answerD": "Brigham"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who wrote and recorded the song \"Talkin about a Revolution\" in 1988? ",
        "correct": "Tracy Chapman",
        "answerA": "Tracy Chapman",
        "answerB": "Mary J Blige",
        "answerC": "Macy Gray",
        "answerD": "Suzanne Vega"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- What smooth 1960's R&B artist recorded the civil rights anthem \"A Change is Gonna Come\"?",
        "correct": "Sam Cooke",
        "answerA": "Sam Cooke",
        "answerB": "Barry White",
        "answerC": "Otis Redding",
        "answerD": "Wilson Pickett"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Winona LaDuke, a Native American activist and former Green Party candidate for office, worked with this folk rock duo to start the grassroots environmental group Honor the Earth.",
        "correct": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerA": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerB": "Simon and  Garfunkel",
        "answerC": "Captain and Tennille",
        "answerD": "Hall and Oats"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- In the 1971 classic album \"What's Going On\" this soul artist tackles everything from racism to the Vietnam War to environmental degradation. Who was the artist? ",
        "correct": "Marvin Gaye",
        "answerA": "Marvin Gaye",
        "answerB": "Curtis Mayfield",
        "answerC": "Smoky Robinson",
        "answerD": "Peter Frampton"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- How old was the pop singer Leslie Gore when she recorded the early women's lib hit \"You Don't Own Me\" in 1963?",
        "correct": "17",
        "answerA": "17",
        "answerB": "30",
        "answerC": "45",
        "answerD": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which one of these bands never released a song about a \"racist friend?\"",
        "correct": "Rise Against",
        "answerA": "Rise Against",
        "answerB": "They Might Be Giants",
        "answerC": "Naomi Pilgrim",
        "answerD": "Special AKA"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL MUSIC MIX- Finish the title of this Joe Hill song written in 1913 and covered in 1984 by Billy Bragg. \"There is power in a _______\"? ",
        "correct": "union",
        "answerA": "union",
        "answerB": "friendship",
        "answerC": "nation",
        "answerD": "family"
    }
]